你好劲呀
Ohh, you're so good.
哦 是的 哪个有我威猛
Ohh, yes. I am the best, baby.
- 哦 耶 - 哦 那肯定是个咪咪
- Oh, yeah! - Oh. Oh, that was a tit.
肯定是咪咪
That is a tit! Yes!
哦 你好巨型
Oh, you're so big!
哦耶 说得对 宝贝
Oh, yeah. Yeah, that's right, baby.
- 有一只钻洞鼠蠢蠢欲动 - 耶
- Oh, doggie wants to hide his bone. - Yes!
宝贝 我要钻进去了 宝贝
Oh, yeah! I'm bone smugglin', baby.
色狼 闭嘴啦
Man, would you shut up!
嘿 吉姆 我是来说晚安的
Hey, Jimmy. Just wanted to say sweet dreams.
嗯 嗯 晚安 妈妈
Yeah, yeah. Sweet dreams. Good night, Mom.
亲一下 晚安
Kiss good night.
- 接收有毛病吗？- 嗯…是的 没错
- Something wrong with the reception? - Uh, yeah. Yeah.
- 我正在看野生动物节目 - 脱掉
- There's… There's this nature show that I'm trying to watch. - Take it off.
- 画面上的麻雀都看不清楚 - 干我 爽
- And the birds are all scrambled and I can't even… - Do me! Yes!
宝贝 当我是马来骑吧
Baby! Ride me like a pony!
遥控器被我坐着 可能坐坏了
The thing must be broken or I sat on the remote or something.
- 还没上床吗 儿子？- 嗯 随时都可以
- Getting ready for bed, son? - Yup, I'm all set, Dad. I'm all set.
- 是吗？- 不不…他可能在看限制频道
- Yeah? - No! No, I think he's tried to watch some illegal channels.
- 限…限制频道？- 只是接收不清楚罢了
- Illegal… Illegal channels? - This is just bad reception, honey.
- 哦 我给个屁股给你打！- 什么？
- Oh, spank my hairy ass! - What's that?
- 哦 宝贝 - 来 把遥控器给我
- Ooh, baby! - You know what? Here. Just give me this, please…
好了 我来 这玩意儿怎么没反应？
Okay, okay. Let's, uh… What the hell's the matter with this thing?
耶
Yes!
《美国派》
限制频道？狗屁
Illegal channels? Shit!
妇女台才是限制频道
If there's any channel that should be illegal, it's that "all- woman's" channel.
- 专门推销丝袜之类的废物 - 就是
- Lifetime supply of pantyhose or some shit. - Yeah.
有没有看电视卡通片《美人鱼》
Hey, uh, did you see The Little Mermaid on TV the other night?
- 没有 - 那个雅莉爱真是风骚
- No. - Ariel, man. She's so hot!
- 她是一条鱼啊 傻瓜 - 上岸就变成美人啦
- Yeah, Oz. But not when she's on land. - She's a mermaid, dude.
维琪 史勒开派对 我们都去 会很好玩的
Come on, Vicky, it's Stifler's party. We got to go. It'll be great.
有什么好玩的 离不开酒和色
Why? All that happens at Stifler's parties is people get drunk and do it.
对
Yeah.
打开来看看 凯文
Now, come on, Kevin. Open it.
又大又厚 你被录取了
It's a big, thick envelope, Vicky. You got in.
那你就打开来看看吧
If you think so, just open it.
好
Fine.
嗯
Hmm.
维琪小姐敬启 很抱歉 本校经过考虑
"Dear Miss Latham: We're sorry but after keeping you on the waiting list…
决定以后都不会录取你
for the past couple of months, we've decided that you are now rejected."
闭嘴
Shut up!
- 你被录取了 - 我爱你
- You got in. - Yes! I love you!
好
Okay.
嘿 你觉得我穿这件衣服去派对 好吗？
Hey, you think I should wear this shirt to Stifler's party?
你已经穿了三天 伙计
You've worn that shirt for, like, three days in a row, man!
各位 她说了
Guys. She said it.
- 说了什么？- 她说他爱我
- Said what? - She said she loves me.
- 糟糕 居然示起爱来了 - 哦 伙计
- Holy shit, dude! The "L" word? - Oh, man!
康乃尔大学 离密西根大学并不远
Cornell's not that far from "U" of "M."
对 只有七个小时的车
Yeah, it's only, like, seven hours.
哦 还要横越加拿大
Oh, and you get to drive across Canada.
- 美丽极了 - 远了点 见面还是行的
- Beautiful country. - Whatever. It's doable.
今天我们不如把乐谱…
Wh- What we should do today, in band.
倒过来吹奏 由尾奏到头
Instead of playing our instruments regularly, we should play them backwards.
- 一定很有趣 - 没错
- That'll be so funny! - Yeah.
不是打击你 你得想想上大学后要如何处理你们的远距离恋爱
No offense, but you're talking about a post- high school, long- distance relationship.
更何况你俩还没有做过
And you and Kevin haven't even done it yet.
我们谈心 不是谈身
That's not why we're going out.
难道他将来去看你 只是吃点心？
What do you expect him to drive to Cornell for? Milk and cookies?
我们打算等待最佳的时机
We're gonna have sex when he's ready and I'm ready.
你是完美主义者
It's got to be completely perfect.
时间地点都要恰到好处
I want the right time, the right moment, the right place…
你们不是上太空 是上床
Vicky, it's not a space shuttle launch. It's sex.
- 芬奇 - 我们正要找你
- Finch. - Here's the man we are looking for.
- 各位 - 怎样了？哥们
- Gentlemen. - What's goin' on, buddy?
- 一样… - 芬奇 你的拉丁文功课做好没有？
- Same ol'… - Finch. You got the Latin homework?
哦
Oh.
意思是「功课给狗吞掉」
It means, "My dog ate it." It's Latin. It's a joke.
- 那是拉丁语玩笑 - 喝咖啡吧 芬奇
- It's a Latin joke. - Yeah, Latin. Just drink your coffee.
- 不 吉姆 这是热饮 - 什么？
- No, Jim, it's mochaccino. - What?
我喝的不是咖啡 是巧克力热饮
What I'm drinking, it's mochaccino. It's not coffee.
情圣！
'Nova!
什么事？
What's up, dude?
今晚派对你来吗？
You comin' to the party tonight, Ozzie, you fuckface?
那要看能不能推掉约会
Uh, depends if my date wants to stop by.
- 假如我的新女友有兴趣去 - 奉劝你们一句
- I'm workin' on somethin' new. - I got an idea about something new.
最好让你们的小和尚见见世面
How about you guys actually locate your dicks,
不要再做处男
remove the shrink- wrap and fucking use them!
我会的 我的女友是大学生
Dude, it's gonna happen. She's a college chick.
哦 那好 今晚见
Oh, right. I'll see you guys tonight.
我会为你们设制个「处男区」
I'll look for you in the no- fucking section.
好的 九点零五分 我会到场
All right. I'm shooting for a 9:00 E.T.A. Beer in hand by five after.
出口气
Breath check.
谢谢
Thank you.
- 会不会太难看？- 今晚有没有追妞的计划？
- I wish you wouldn't do that. - So, you got something up your sleeve for tonight?
我已胸有成竹
This is a foolproof plan, my friend.
我有很多问题想问你
I have a serious question to ask you guys. Okay.
那个来自捷克的交换生娜迪雅今晚可能会去
You know Nadia the Czechoslovakian chick? She might be there tonight.
那么…你们认为她喜欢
Now, do you think she would prefer…
我这个稳定型
Laid- back Jim…
又或者…
or…
酷帅型
Cool, hip Jim?
凭你那样的衣服 什么型都没用
I don't think it really matters with that shirt you're wearing.
什么？你女朋友任你摸
What? Correct me if I'm wrong but you're the one with the girlfriend…
你当然说话大声
and you're still stranded on third base.
嘿 起码我可以摸 好不好？
Hey, at least I know what third base feels like, okay?
- 至今只有摸自己 - 坏家伙 坏家伙
- You're still just a batboy. - Batboy. Batboy.
各位 嗯…
Guys, uh…
摸上去有什么样的感觉？
What exactly does third base feel like?
你回答吧
You wanna take this one?
- 像个热苹果派 - 是吗？- 是的
- Like warm apple pie. - Yeah? - Yeah.
- 苹果派？- 嗯哼
- Apple pie, huh? - Uh-huh.
麦当劳的还是自己做的？
McDonald's or homemade?
各位 我们有使命要完成
Gentlemen, destiny awaits.
这是我喝的第五和第六杯
That's number five and six for the Stif- meister!
耶
Yeah.
糟糕
Oops!
- 真正点 - 嘿
- Holy! - Hey!
娜迪雅 你好 欢迎欢迎
Nadia! Buenos dias. Glad you could make it.
等一下再谈
I'll be back for you later.
- 派对开始 - 你在干嘛？
- Another party sultan! - How ya doin'?
欢迎光临史勒的爱情温床
Welcome to Stifler's Palace of Love, fellas.
- 啤酒在那里 不要客气 - 好
- The keg's back there! Enjoy! - Yeah.
维琪 杰西卡 欢迎你们
Vicky, Jessica! Great to see you. Glad you could make it.
哈哈 贱货们
Haha, bitches!
- 雪门！- 嘿
- Sherman! - Hey!
你也来了 有何贵干？
What the fuck are you doin' here?
你们在做什么？
Fellas! What's goin' on?
小伙子们 有何贵干？
没什么 希望能追到女该
Sherman. Not much. Just, uh, scopin' the babes.
- 确实 这里美女如云 - 是啊
- Indeed! Some fine ladies here, boys. - Uh-huh.
信心十足 重复 信心十足
Confidence is high. Repeat. Confidence is high.
我雪门进入二级临战状态
Sherman is movin' to DEFCON 2.
- 随时准备出击 - 嘿
- Full strategic arsenal ready for deployment. - Hey!
你有没有目标？雪门
You have somethin' goin' tonight, Sherman?
有没有看到中区高中那褐发女孩
You see that Central chick, Bernette?
- 嗯…没有 - 没有
- Um, no. - No.
她来了 似乎时我有意思
She's around. Seems she's taken a liking to me.
我决定让她见识一下…雪门终结者
Fellas, it's time she experienced… the Shermanator.
雪门 你爱怎样说都行
Yeah, okay, Sherman. Whatever.
我是跨越时空的性爱机械人
I'm a sophisticated sex robot sent back through time…
女人遇到我 她就走运了
to change the future for one lucky lady.
- 出动吧 虎哥 - 我会回来的
- Go get 'em, tiger. - I'll be back!
- 无可救药 - 死要面子
- Hopeless. - Completely.
- 嗨 - 嘿 维琪
- Hi. - Hey, Vic.
哦 糟糕 各位 各位…
Oh, shit. Guys… Guys…
娜迪雅在那里
There's Nadia and she just looked at me.
- 她看了我一眼 - 为什么不过去聊聊？
- She just looked at me. - Well, why don't you go talk to her?
对
Yeah.
对 我应该去跟她聊聊
Yeah, you're right, Kev. I should just go talk to her.
对 我办得到
Yeah, I could do that. Sure.
没错
Sure.
凯文？凯文？凯…
Kev? Kev? Ke…
是啊 是
Yeah. Yeah.
真是好玩
That's great!
再见
See ya later.
我们是来参加派对的
We're here for the party.
什么派对？没有派对啊
What party? There's no party.
奇怪 去那边看看吧
Weird. Try the house down the street.
那…你主修哪一科？
So, what's your major?
从现代妇权思潮
Post- modern feminist thought.
哦 厉害 看夜色多美
Oh, cool. Great night, isn't it?
确实
Sure.
对 春天是可爱的季节 不是吗？
Yeah, it's just somethin' about the springtime that's just cool, you know?
- 春雨过后气息最清新 - 嗯
- Like the smell of fresh rain or somethin'. - Mmm.
帮我吹吧 美女
Suck me, beautiful.
你刚刚说什么？
What did you just say?
帮我吹吧 美女
Suck me, beautiful.
朋友叫我做情圣 即是大情大圣
My friends call me "'Nova, " as in Casanova.
真刻薄
That's pathetic.
天啊 不要取笑我
Jeez, you don't have to laugh at me.
好吧 你最好改一改态度 这最重要
Well, there's just some things you need to learn, that's all.
- 怎样改？- 放自然一点
- Like what? - Well, you've got to tone it down.
你想营造浪漫气氛…
You don't need to come to a place like Lookout Point…
不一定要装模作样
and spout off cheeseball lines to be romantic.
- 好的 - 对女孩要温柔体贴
- Okay. - You have to pay attention to a girl.
理解她的感受 感情是双方面的
Be sensitive to her feelings. Relationships are reciprocal.
来吧 情圣 我还是送你回你朋友那里
Come on, Casanova. I'll take you back to your friends.
维琪 我们是否应该有进一步的发展
Vicky, think it's time to take the next step in our relationship?
- 今晚？- 对 你一直向往完美气氛…
- Tonight? - Yeah, it's such a perfect evening.
我说是 今晚不正是吗？
I mean, it's how you've always pictured it, isn't it?
干 我的屁真臭啊
Damn, my parts fuckin' stink!
伙计 你就像吃屎了一样 闻起来真恶心
Dude, you gotta take a shit! You smell like a Yeti!
或者还不是
Or not.
躺下来
Just relax.
你真的那样说？
You actually said that?
闭嘴
Shut up!
我比你更失败
You did a hell of a lot better than I did with Nadia.
哦 谢谢你的鼓励 我舒服多了
Oh, thanks, Jim, that's great. That's really reassuring.
不用客气 情圣
Hey, no problem, 'Nova.
别再叫我情圣 我只是虚有其名
Hey, don't call me 'Nova anymore. I'm a… I'm a fraud.
全都是不中用的家伙
You guys are pathetic.
到我大显身手了
I'm gonna find myself a little hottie.
帮我吹吧 美女
"Suck me, beautiful"!
- 记得先出声 - 好
- Let me know. - Okay.
继续
Keep going.
按道理我应该和女孩谈得来
I should be able to talk to girls.
我也能说会道
I'm articulate.
语言科我得到720分
You know, I got a 720 on my S.A.T. Verbal.
废话 哪管屁用
Bullshit. There's no way.
真的没骗你 你听着
I kid you not, man. Look. Listen.
- 滔滔不止 似是而非 - 嗯
- Copious. Verisimilitude. - Mmm.
哦 哦 来了
Oh, ohh. Now.
哦
Ohh.
帮我吹吧 美女！
Suck me, beautiful!
- 该死 史勒 - 时间到了
- Damn it, Stifler. - Checkout time!
- 请退房 - 真是坏蛋！
- Please, vacate the room. - You are such a jerk.
天啊 你这派对有许多很酷的学长
God, I can't believe how many cool people are at this party.
没错
Yup.
你真是大方
And you got a keg too!
- 哇哦 - 当然
- Wow! - Indeed.
哦 等一等 我的啤酒忘记拿上来了
Oh, wait. I left my beer downstairs.
别啊 喝这杯吧
No. No. Here, babe!
谢谢
Thanks.
你的样子好甜美 哦…
You're really beautiful. Oh…
- 真的？- 是的
- Really? - Oh, yeah.
你知道吗？我现在比较矛盾
You know what? I don't know if I want to be doing this.
- 为什么？- 如果我们今晚相好…
- Doing what? - You know, like, if we hook up tonight,
明天你肯定到处乱说
tomorrow I'll just be some girl you go telling all your friends about.
绝对不会
No way!
你要发誓 但你应该看着我说
Steve, you could at least look at me when you say that!
听着 莎拉
Look. Sarah,
我…我不会到处乱说的
I… I wouldn't go telling stories or anything about you.
我保证 所以…你放心好了
I promise. So, just… relax,
慢慢享受…这无限的乐趣吧
take it slow… and let the good times roll.
- 好的 - 好吧
- Okay. - All right.
怎么了？
What's wrong?
什么事啊？
What's wrong? What is it?
蜀犬吠日
Xenophobic.
哦
Oh!
- 五脏翻腾 - 这句成语我体验多了
- Regurgitation. - I know that one.
- 凯文喜欢 - 他不喜欢才怪
- Kevin likes it. - He likes getting head.
你呢？凯文有没有
Gee, what a total shocker. What about you, Vicky?
我是说 凯文难道就没有
I mean, h- have you just never had one with Kevin…
为你制造过高潮？
or have you never had one, period?
有过一次
I've had one.
- 似乎是 - 好吧
- I think. - Okay.
就是说没有试过 难怪你没有兴趣
That's a no. No wonder you're not psyched about sex.
你从来没有自慰过？
You tell me you never even had one manually?
哈哈 真精彩
Ha- ha, nice!
天啊 史勒你究竞喝了多少酒？
Jesus! Stifler, how much did you drink, man?
嘿 史勒 豆浆好味道吗？
Hey, Stifler? How's the pale ale?
- 你去死吧 - 哦 喔
- Fuck you! - Ooh, whoo!
- 那是史勒的妈妈？- 是的
- That's Stifler's mom? - Yup.
妈的 难以制信 这样风骚的女人…却生了史勒那种儿子
Shit. I cannot believe a fine woman like this produced a guy like Stifler.
- 伙计 她是痰伯母 - 你说什么玩意？
- Dude, that chick's a "MILF." - What the hell is that?
- 痰伯母…令我起痰的伯母 - 没错 伙计
- M-I-L-F… Mom I'd like to fuck. - Yeah, dude!
哦哦 耶
Oh- ho, yeah!
- 耶 痰伯母… - 嘿 你们两个…
- Yeah! MILF! MILF! - Hey, guys… Guys. Guys.
- 过来 - 什么事？雪门
- Come here. - Sherman, what's goin' on?
嗯…你们说话可不可以收敛一点？
Yeah, uh… Don't you think you fellas could try a little tact?
我要应酬人 明白吗？
I got company, if you know what I mean?
她很正点
She's hot!
假如给雪门抢先…我咽不下这口气
If Sherman has sex before I do, I'm gonna be really pissed.
雪门 雪门终结者？
Sherman? The Shermanator?
走吧
Come on, man.
痰伯母…
MILF! MILF!
痰伯母！嘿 你在做什么？伙计
MILF! MILF! Dude, hey, dude. What are you doin' to her, dude?
哦 天啊 伙计
Oh, my God, bro, dude.
吹来吹去一场空
Enough of this blow job bullshit.
- 我要来真的 - 说得好 真是好
- I gotta get laid already. - That's nice. Really, really nice.
- 载我去 好吗？- 当然可以
- Can I have a ride? - Sure.
- 维琪 等一等 - 你值得我等吗？
- Vicky, wait. - Not for you.
真丢人！我真丢人！
Yeti! I am the Yeti!
- 各位 早晨 - 芬奇
- Good morning, gentlemen. - Finch.
你昨晚怎样？不是胸有成竹吗？
Where were you last night, huh? What happened to that foolproof plan of yours?
我太过稳定 来得太迟 等到来的时候
Well, I was going for a fashionably- late entrance and I was too late.
女孩已经都走了
So, no ladies left.
昨晚很珍贵 一刻值千金
It was a very special night, very special.
各位 各位
Guys. Guys.
- 我永远不会忘记 - 哦 我也不会
- I'll never forget this. - Oh, I'll never forget it, either.
- 谢谢你 - 嗯
- Thank you. - Uhh.
- 再见 - 再见
- Well, bye. - Bye.
再见
Bye.
各位 跟花痴雪门说声再见
Fellas, say good- bye to Chuck Sherman, the boy.
我现在…是男人了
I… am now a man.
足以成为你们的榜样
I highly recommend you join the club.
我们搞得翻天覆地足足一个通宵 害得我现在筋疲力尽
We were doin' the wild thing… all night. I'm exhausted.
我不明白 你到底是怎样追到的？
I don't get it. I mean, how the hell did you do that?
我没有怎样追 只是水到渠成
It was just my time. It was just my time.
小伙子们 祝你们好运
Best of luck to you boys.
- 难以制信 - 别这样 伙计们
- I cannot believe this. - Come on, guys.
我们应该看开点 替雪门高兴
You know, we should be happy for Sherman.
你叫我们如何能高兴起来？
No, we shouldn't be.
我追维琪追了好几个月
You know, I put in months of quality time with Vicky.
雪门当晚就追到 简直没道理
Sherman meets a chick for one night and scores.
- 真是太没道理了 - 一坨屎
- This is just wrong. - No shit.
究竞怎样才算温柔体贴呢？
How the hell am I supposed to become Mr. Sensitive Man?
看情形我们一定会成处男大学生 对吧？
You know, we're all gonna go to college as virgins. You realize this, right?
大学可能没有处男宿舍
I mean, they probably have special dorms for people like us.
好 我有个提议 我们四个人…
All right. I got an idea. But it's got to stay between us.
很简单 我们订个秘密协议
It's really simple. We just got to make an agreement.
嗯…不仅是个协议 更是个…
Er, nah. It's… It's more than an agreement.
- 什么？打赌？- 合作
- What? A bet? - A pact.
不仅仅是打赌 而是同盟
No money involved. More important than any bet.
我们痛下决心 决心争取在毕业前开斋
Here's the deal. We all get laid before we graduate.
伙计 说的容易 我到现在都无功而退
Dude, it's not like I haven't been trying to get laid.
这情形就像做运动 做运动要有人在旁边鼓励 对吧？
Think about when you work out, Oz. You gotta have someone there, right?
当有人停下来 其他人要督促他继续
Someone to spot you. Someone to keep you motivated.
这样才做得起劲 我们互相勉励
Well, that's exactly what we can do for each other.
我是指 互相鞭策监督
I mean, we'll be there to keep each other on track.
分散我们力量薄弱的部分 团结在一起
Separately, we are flawed and vulnerable, but together,
我们雄风大振
we are the masters of our sexual destiny.
你有五爪金龙
Their tiger- style kung fu is strong.
我有树下偷桃
But our dragon- style will defeat it.
- 各位 - 少林老祖一出山
- Guys! - The Shaolin masters from East and West must unite!
- 且看鹿死谁手 - 各位
- Fight, and find out who is number one. - Guys!
不要打岔 破坏气氛 我们想抬得起头…
Come on. You're ruining my moment here. This is our very manhood at stake.
现在就要拿出决心来
We must make a stand, here and now.
不准我的老二再软弱无力
No longer will our penises remain flaccid and unused!
不准无精打彩必须一展所长
We will fight for every man out there who isn't getting laid and should be.
这是我们的奋斗目标
This is our day. This is our time.
我们的光荣使命 决不做一辈子处男
And, by God, we will not stand by and watch history condemn us into celibacy.
- 对啊 - 说到我心坎里了
- Amen. Yes. - I like that.
- 排除万难 不达到目的誓不罢休 - 早就应该这样
- We will make a stand. We will succeed. - 'Bout time!
- 我们一定要做得了爱 - 对 - 对
- We will get laid! - Yeah! - Yeah!
那么…关于所做的爱 必须你情我愿
Now, the sex: It's got to be valid, consensual sex.
不得召妓 尤其是你 芬奇
No prostitutes. That's what you're thinkin', Finch.
被人识穿了
Busted.
因此 毕业舞会是我们最后的机会
So, basically, prom is our last chance.
- 毕业舞会最没意思 - 同意
- Oh, dude. Prom sucks. - I know,
但舞会之后的派对是大好良机
but you gotta think about it this way.
我是说 我们可以事半功倍 女孩们会自动献身
I mean, all the parties afterwards? The chicks are going to want to do it.
- 对 他说得对 - 好像已经成为一年一次的献身节
- Yeah, yeah, he's right. It's, like tradition or something. - The Rose Bowl.
- 毕业舞会离现在… - 足足三个星期
- So, that gives us… - Exactly three weeks to the day.
- 我们誓死往前迈进 - 好 往前迈进 - 往前迈进
- We're gonna do this. - All right, to the next step! - Next step!
往前迈进
Next step!
（瀑布谷花店）
（网上媒人 我们撮合有情人）
收到我的花没有？
Well, did you get the flowers?
（有兴趣做你女友的人数：0）
（超快感安全套）
别担心 她会重投你怀抱
Don't worry. You'll get her back soon enough.
- 你认为会吗？- 当然 她喜欢你
- You think so? - Sure, she likes you.
- 我也喜欢她 - 你爱她吗？
- Well, I like her too. - Do you love her?
这个问题太难回答了
Um, you know what? You can't really ask me that.
你要骗她床 就在说我爱你
Well, if you want to get her in the sack, I mean, just tell her you love her.
- 我就是这样被人骗掉 - 听着 杰西卡
- That's how I was duped. - Look, Jessica,
我…我不想骗她
I- I don't want to dupe her.
好吧 那你就得…
All right. What you need to do…
懂得讨她欢心
is learn how to press a girl's buttons.
帮她到达快乐的境界
You have to give her what she's never had.
- 指的是什么？- 给你个提示
- What's that? - Let me give you a hint.
噢 凯文…嗯 耶
Ohh, Kev! Uhh. Yeah.
- 明白吗？- 你是指高潮？
- Comprende? - You mean an orgasm.
- 对了 大情人 - 嗯…你知道
- You got it, stud! - Well, you know,
我…我明明给过她…
I'm- I'm pretty sure that I've… given her a…
- 不 你没有 - 试过有一次
- No, you haven't. - Well, there was one time…
- 没有 - 哦 天啊
- No. - Oh, man.
- 用性或用爱 任君选择 - 傻瓜
- Look, kid, it's up to you. The big "L" or the big "O." - Dickhead!
你们得来看看热闹
You gotta see this.
他为什么会变成这样？
What did you cocks do to him?
好 下次再见
Great. See you next time.
- 嘿 来欣赏我的歌喉？- 是啊
- Hey, guys. Came to watch me in action? - Yeah.
- 你唱得不错 - 没错 伙计
- I think you sounded pretty good. - Yeah, man.
我认为你做了变性手术
I think you need your balls reattached.
- 小声点 - 你在这里做什么？
- Hey, keep it down, dude. - What the fuck are you doing here?
这是块处女地
This place is an untapped resource.
我是说 看那里
I mean, check it out.
- 女歌手好漂亮 - 他到现在才参加合唱班
- These vocal jazz girls are hot. - Why the hell is he joining jazz choir so late?
可能自知会留级 准备后路
Maybe he's preparing for another senior year at East?
不要乱猜 我们根本不认识他
You guys, we don't even know him.
你真没出息
You dipshit!
连合唱团的乖乖女…
You're expecting to score with some…
…你都想追？
goody- goody choirgirl priss?
这些女生不知道我来历 我可以采取体贴攻势
These chicks don't know me. I can work the sensitive angle here, fellas!
照足那大学女孩所教
You know, it's just like that college chick told me.
只要逗她们说话
All that you gotta do is just ask 'em questions…
然后扮聆听者
and listen to what they have to say and shit.
这样一来 岂不委屈了自己
I don't know, man. That sounds like a lot of work!
嗯…等一等
Uh, just a second!
进来 进来吧
Come in. Come in.
哦 吉姆 原来你在这里
Oh, Jim, you're here.
嗯…我刚经过你门口
Uh, I was just walking by your room and uh…
突然想起 你我父子俩好久没有…
And, you know, I was thinking, "Boy, it's been a long time since we've had…
详细谈过了
a little father-son, Uh-uh, chat."
哦 差点忘了 我买了几本杂志
Oh! I almost forgot. I, uh, I bought some magazines.
你可以翻到中间的插页
Do you just want to flip to the center section?
这个是…这是个女性的身体
Well, this is the… this is the, uh, female form.
摄影师把焦点放在胸脯上
And they have focused on the breasts,
胸脯主要是用来哺乳 也是用来…爱抚
uh, which are used primarily to, uh, feed young infants…
- 嗯…这本杂志叫… - 好的
- and, uh… and also, uh, in foreplay. - Right.
另外这本杂志叫…《卖春》
This is, uh… This is Hustler.
风格更加露骨
And this is a much more exotic magazine.
摄影师故意…把焦点放在 私处
Now, they have decided to focus on the, uh, pubic region…
- 对 - 整个三角地带
- Right. Uh-huh. - The whole groin area.
看着她的脸 明白吗？明白她在干什么吗？
Look at the expression on her face. You see that? See what's she's doing?
她仿佛在对你说
She's kind of looking right into your eyes saying,
「嘿 帅哥 你在干嘛」
"Hey, big boy. Hey, how ya doin'?"
- 看到了吗？- 看到了
- You see? - Right.
《剃毛》这本杂志我并不熟悉
Shaved is a magazine I'm not too familiar with,
不过 你再翻到中间的…
but, again, if you flip to the center…
插页…
Section…
会察觉到那里一览无遗
Well, you see the detail that, uh, that they go into in this picture here.
- 嗯…是的 - 一眼看去 像块热带树叶
- Uh-huh. Yeah. - It almost looks like a tropical plant or something…
- 也像某种海味 - 是的
- underwater… thing. - Yeah. Yes.
- 知道阴蒂是什么吗？- 噢 天啦！
- Do you know what a clitoris is? - Oh, my God.
- 别说「噢」 是的 - 我知道阴蒂是什么
- Well, don't say, "Oh…" - Yes, I know what a clitoris is.
哦 你知道 我明白了 原来你知道 你知道得可真丰富
Oh, you do. Oh, I see. Yes, you do. I forgot you've been there and back.
- 你什么都知道 - 我想方设法这样…
- You know everything… - I've learned about it in Sex Ed…
- 你知道什么？对不起 - 不不不…
- You know what? I'm sorry. Okay? I'm sorry. - No- no- no.
- 对不起 很对不起 - 我很对不起
- I'm sorry. I'm sorry. - I'm sorry.
我不应该生气
I shouldn't have got hot there.
这样吧接下来我将会…
Well, you know what I'm going to do, Jim.
把杂志放在这里 然后离开
I'm going to just leave these books here…
交给你 你可以慢慢欣赏
for you to, uh, peruse at your, uh… at your leisure.
等一等
Wait!
好吧 总比用长筒袜安全
Well, safer than a tube sock.
- 好…很高兴和你聊天 - 是
- Okay, that… That was good. - Yeah.
- 晚餐见 - 嗯…好 晚餐见
- See you at dinner. - Uh, yeah. I'll see you at dinner.
你想用高尔夫球追女孩？
So, Finch, this is your plan?
你知道 但女孩不喜欢高尔夫球
You know, I don't think girls are into the whole mini- golf thing.
凯文 她们当然不喜欢
Kevin, I'm sure that they're not.
实际上 有件事我需要你们合作
Actually, there is one small matter that I need to ask for your cooperation in.
- 大家既然是盟友 对吧？- 当然 什么事？
- In the spirit of this whole pact, you know? - Sure, what do you need?
无论别人人怎说我 你们都同意
Whatever you hear about me, you agree. And tell all the boys the same thing.
现在我要回家一趟
Look, I gotta go. Sixteen minutes round- trip.
芬奇 你是高中生了
You know, Finch, it's… it's senior year.
我是说 你现在还怕在学校上厕所？
I mean, don't you think it's time you learned how to take a dump at school?
校厕的环境 难道你没看见吗？
When was the last time you looked at the facilities in this school?
请问
Excuse me.
嗯…刚刚是保罗芬奇吗？
Uh, that's Paul Finch, right?
- 是的 - 你和他用同一间更衣室
- Yeah. - Well, you've seen him in the locker room, right?
- 是的 - 那…我的朋友都想知道 是真还是假？
- Uh, yeah. - So, my friends, they want to know. Is it true?
他的老二是不是很大？
You know, that he's… equipped.
不知道 芬奇穿着浴袍沐浴
I have no idea. Finch showers with his bathing suit on.
我是说…
I mean, uh…
老实说…是真的 简直是巨无霸
As a matter of fact, it is true. The guy's huge!
- 毕业舞会他有舞伴吗？- 没有 肯定没有
- Does he have a date for the prom yet? - No, definitely not.
好的 谢谢
All right. Thanks.
哦 厉害
Oh, man!
哥哥 可不可以教我一下？
So I was thinking maybe you could give me some advice, brother to brother.
有什么秘诀可以令她产生…
I thought you might know a trick or somethin' to make her…
- 高潮？- 是的 - 有什么好东西吗？
- Orgasm? - Yeah. - What's good here?
- 你怎么办？- 嘿 不要介意 注意听…
- How do you do that? - Hey, never mind that. Listen, pay attention.
你的目标是什么？只求能上床？
Is that all that you're interested in, tryin' to get your girl into bed?
不 她给了我不少快乐 做为回报…
No, it'd be good to be able to, you know, return the favor.
我希望能她也能得到快乐
Be nice to know she enjoys things as much as I do.
这样啊？很好 这才像话 你现在够资格了
See that? That's good. That's what I wanted to hear. Now, you qualify.
- 够什么资格？- 够资格继承《性经》
- Qualify for what? - My man, you've just inherited the Bible.
图书馆里秘藏着一本性爱指南
It originally started as a sex manual,
这本书是从阿姆斯特丹带回来的
this book that some guys brought back from Amsterdam.
每年由够资格的学生辗转相传
And each year it got passed on to one East student who was worthy.
现在上面累积了大量得主笔记
Now, it's full of all sorts of stuff that guys have added over the years.
千万不要公开 看完放回去
But you have to keep it a secret and return it at the end of the year.
好了 话已经说完 祝你好运
All right. So now you know. Good luck.
你在唱什么？
What was that?
- 嗯…对不起 - 不 唱得很好啊
- Uh, sorry. - No, it was good.
我只是即兴唱出心声
Well, it, uh… It came from the heart.
好 继续 大家唱得很好
Well, keep it coming. All right, people, good work!
记着 还有两星期就是歌唱比赛
Now, don't forget. The state competition's a couple of weeks away,
大家加把劲 好吗？
so keep on it, okay?
不错啊 基斯
Not bad, Chris.
真的？
Really?
谢谢 你叫海瑟 对不对？
Thanks, uh, Heather, right?
是的
Yeah.
你唱法兰仙纳杜拉腔
So, you've got this sort of Frank Sinatra thing going on.
对 我最近才发现自己有音乐细胞
Right. I feel like I've discovered this whole new side of me.
音乐最能表达感情
I mean, uh, music is so expressive.
很好 我是说…我同意 但…
Okay. I mean, I agree, but…
你经常在球场上拼搏…
aren't you supposed to be out, like, trying to decapitate someone…
- 抽得出时间来练歌吗？- 哦 当然
- with your lacrosse stick or something? - Oh, sure. Sure.
我知道大家对我的看法
You know, I know what people think. It's like,
「欧兹只是个浑球」
"Oz, he's just this kick- ass lacrosse player."
你知道 我确实喜欢打球 顺便说一下 即便如此
You know, I also play football, by the way, but that's, like,
- 但我不仅仅是个球员 - 当然 我并不…
- that's not all that I am, you know? - Of course, I didn't…
被人否定 我总觉得不公平
I mean, it really bothers me when people try to pigeonhole me like that.
你啊
You?
你认为我不了解么？
You think I don't get that?
因为我不喝酒喝到一塌糊涂…
God, it's like just because I don't get drunk and barf every weekend…
人家就把我形容为假正经
that people say, "Oh, look. There's this Goody Two- Shoes choirgirl priss."
那么你除了唱歌 还有什么活动？
Yeah. So, like, what else do you do?
跟你一样
Well, the same things you do,
和朋友一起
like hang out with friends and stuff.
- 你以为我会有什么活动？- 哦 我…
- Why? What do you think I do? - Oh, I…
说起来 我对你一无所知
I just realized that I don't know anything about you.
- 不过我有兴趣知道 - 我希望能够多了解你
- I was interested. - Oh, well, what do you want to know?
你知道…我也想了解你
You know, stuff… about you.
好吧
All right.
妈 无回来了
Mom, I'm home!
（吉姆 你爱吃的苹果派 妈妈）
哦 耶 哦
Oh, yeah. Oh!
- 吉姆？- 并不是你想的那样
- Jim! - It's not what it looks like.
那么…我只好告诉你妈妈 嗯…那什么…
Well, we'll just tell your mother that, uh… that, uh…
我们把苹果批吃掉了
we ate it all.
（注意：胆小勿效舌头秘笈）
8号欧兹入球
Goal by number eight, Chris Ostreicher.
- 精彩的比赛 - 精彩的比赛
- Nice game. - Nice game. Good game.
嘿 你来看球？
Hey, what are you doin' here?
我是第一次来 特来欣赏你的精湛球技
Just enjoying my first exhilarating lacrosse experience.
- 你很厉害 - 哦 谢谢
- You kicked butt. - Oh, thanks.
- 嗯 基斯 - 你可以叫我欧兹
- Um, Chris… - Oh, you can call me Oz, if you want.
- 我一定要吗？- 或者欧兹卡
- Do I have to? - You can call me Ostreicher.
- 你还有什么名字？- 啊 算了
- What's your middle name? - Nah, forget it.
- 我不会告诉别人 - 我也不会
- Come on. I won't tell anyone. - Well, neither will I.
好吧…嗯
Okay. Um.
我有个提议
So, I had this thought and…
说出来似乎冒昧
It may seem like it's way out of left field.
但不知你的意思是怎样 我没有男朋友 或者…
I don't know if you can, but since I'm not going with anybody, I thought that maybe…
他们全都是饭桶
Those guys sucked ass!
合唱团的小妞 你来干什么？
Choir chick, what the hell are you doing here?
我是来邀请基斯一起参加毕业舞会
Well, uh, I was asking Chris to prom.
那么…你愿意吗？
So, do you want to go?
哦 好啊 太好了
Oh, yeah! That would be great.
别奢望欧兹有豪华车接送
Well, just don't expect Oz to pay for the limo!
史勒 去你的 我是说…
Stifler, fuck! I mean…
你为什么总不能体贴一点？
Why do you got to be so insensitive all the time?
什么？
What?
懒得理你 别忘了 舞会之后有派对
Whatever. Look, uh, don't forget. My cottage after prom.
到我湖畔别墅来
On Lake Michigan.
嘿 等一等 你小子到哪里去？
Hey, wait up, you pussies. Where you goin'?
啊 好吧 我要…我要去洗澡了
Ah, well, I gotta… I gotta hit the showers now,
很高兴一起参加舞会 感觉真的很好
but I think this is gonna be really, really good.
- 嗯 我也是 - 好吧
- Yeah. Me too. - All right.
- 再见 - 再见
- Bye. - Bye. Bye.
- 欧兹 你真行！- 追合唱团的乖乖女？
- Appenin Oz! - Working with the choir chick?
没办法 她穿T恤好迷人
What d'ya say, fellas? I just dig those cute little sweaters she wears.
你艳福不浅啦
Nuts you do, you little horn dog.
耶 耶 宝贝
Yeah! Yeah, baby!
糟蹋我吧 帅哥 叫床叫出高音C来
Spank me! Spank me! Hit that high "C."
你怎样追到的？
Come on! What's goin' on here?
我很自私 根本不体贴
I was being selfish and majorly insensitive.
我是个蠢才 苯蛋 畜牲
I'm a… I'm a total idiot. I mean, a fool, a buffoon.
总之你是个坏蛋
I think shithead really says it.
你说得对 我是个坏蛋 我想补偿你
You know what? You're right. I'm a shithead, and I want to make it up to you.
哦 怎么补偿？
Oh, yeah? How?
哦 哦…哦
Oh. Oh. Oh. Ohh!
维琪 嘘 你爸妈在楼下
Vicky. Shh. Your parents are downstairs.
- 凯文 不要停 - 等一等
- Kevin, don't stop! - Just a second.
（舌功秘笈）
亲爱的 叫维琪下来吃饭好吗？
Hon, can you tell Vic to come on down for supper?
- 真他妈厉害 - 嘘 你的门没有上锁
- Holy shit! - Shh. You know there's no lock on your door?
哦 我来了 我来了
Ohh! I'm coming! I'm coming!
- 吉姆 - 爸爸
- Oh, Jim! - Dad.
嘿 我正在看我们一家的合照
Hi, I was just looking at the old family portrait out here.
当时很开心 对不对？
Well, that was a fun day wasn't it?
- 哦 是的 - 对
- Oh, yeah. - Yeah.
吉姆 我想谈谈自慰
Jim, I want to talk about masturbation.
自慰是绝对正常的行为
Now, I just want you to know that it's- it's a perfectly normal, uh, thing.
无可否认 你知道
And I have to admit, uh, you know.
我年轻时也成天想着上小妞
I did a fair bit of masturbating when I was a little younger.
- 我…嗯… - 我戏称为打手枪
- I, uh… - I used to call it "stroking the salami."
对 还有舞单节辊
Yeah, you know, "pounding the ol' pud."
但我从没用过糕点
I never did it with baked goods.
你的大伯天天都打手枪 每天打五六次
But you know your Uncle Mort? He "pinched the one- eyed snake" five, six times a day.
就像…赛前的练习
See, it's like, uh, practice for the big game.
明白吗？就像…就像…
You see? It's like… It's like…
独自对着墙壁练网球
banging a tennis ball against a brick wall.
虽然能过手瘾 但总不及对打
Which can be fun. It can be fun, but it's not a game.
- 对…嗯 - 这不是比赛
- Right. No. - It's not a game.
对打要有对手 球来球往
What you want is you want a partner to return the ball.
- 你要不要对手？- 嗯 我需要
- Do you want a partner? - Yeah, Yeah, I want a partner.
- 真的要对手？- 哦 真的需要
- You do want a partner? - Oh, I want a partner.
- 你要对手 是好事 - 当然
- Want a partner. Good. Good. - Of course.
很好
Good.
因此 贺尔一旦登基…
So, once Hal becomes king, he has to take on…
就要肩负重任 抛开他的老友…
the responsibilities of leadership and turn his back…
醉汉科士达
on his old, drunken friend, Falstaff.
贺尔面临人生转折点 就像你们一样
You see, Hal is going through a… rite of passage, much like you all are.
你们聚会时光已不多 要好好珍惜
So make most of the time you've got left together. You'll miss it later.
舌头有没有抽筋？
So, does your tongue cramp up?
- 没有 只觉得有点晕 - 哇哦
- Nah. You get kind of dizzy, though. - Wow.
厉害 她可能回味无穷
That's amazing. She's probably gonna want to do it soon.
好了 下课
All right. Class dismissed.
各位 你们依然没开斋吗？
Still questing after the Holy Grail, huh, guys?
嘿 芬奇呢？
Hey, uh, where's Finch?
回家上厕所
Oh, he went home to take a shit.
奇怪 我就是不明白
I don't get it. I just don't.
为什么他突然成名？
How does a guy like that get this sudden reputation?
- 成什么名？- 我来示范
- What reputation? - Observe.
请问 你知道芬奇是谁吗？
Ex- Excuse me. Do you know who Paul Finch is?
知道 他是那个有型的男孩 对吧？
Yeah! He's the guy with the tattoo, right?
就是身上刺有鹰 烈火之类的纹身
You know, the eagle and the blazing fire and that stuff.
你们见到他 代我康妮问候他
Well, um, if you guys see him later, will you tell him Courtney says hi?
再见
Bye.
好 解释吧
Okay. Explain.
解释不了 我也莫明其妙
I can't. I don't know how he's doing it.
这样一来 只有吉姆没有进展
I, uh… I guess that just leaves Jim trailing.
- 啊 吉姆 - 振作起来 伙计
- Aw, Jimbo! - Better sack up, buddy!
是 我知道 我要急起直追了 对吧？
Yeah, I know. I'm working on it, all right?
吉姆
James?
你的历史成绩很好 是不是？
You are very good in the world history class, yes?
我？是 不是…嗯…
Me? Y- Yes. No, uh…
- 是 相当好 - 可不可以教教我？
- Yes, I am. - Perhaps you could help me with my studies.
嗯…好 乐意到极
Uh, yeah. Absolutely.
那…那…那就约个时间吧
Tha- Tha- Tha… That would be… That would be great sometime.
- 明天好吧？- 明天我要练芭蕾舞
- How about tomorrow? - Well, I have ballet practice.
或者练完舞到你家去
Perhaps I could come by your house afterwards?
可以地你家里换衣服
I could change clothes at your place.
哦 嗯…好的
Oh. Uh… yeah.
应该没问题 可以
I suppose that would be okay. Sure.
不错的汽车
Nice car!
- 很高兴你懂欣赏 - 你不喜欢？
- I'm glad you think so. - You don't like it?
不 我喜欢啊 但关于毕业舞会
No, I like the car. By the way, though, about prom?
对不起 我不应该邀请你
That was a bad idea. I'm sorry I invited you.
- 什么意思？- 拜托
- What are you talkin' about? - Please.
我本以为你值得做朋友
I asked you because I thought you might actually be worth going with.
但你只是个浑球 不 你是个坏蛋
But you are just a jock. No, wait. You're a jerk.
等等 我不明白
Wait! I don't understand.
我看见你们一队球员取玩我
I saw you making fun of me with your lacrosse buddies.
海瑟 我并没有取笑你
Heather, I wasn't makin' fun of you.
无需再解释 你是伪君子
Gimme a break. You're so full of it.
真见鬼！东欧女孩到你家里脱衣服
Fuck me! There's gonna be an Eastern European chick naked in your house.
你什么行动也没有？
And you're not gonna do anything about that?
我可以怎样？把她裸照登上网？
What am I gonna do, huh? Broadcast her over the Internet?
- 对啊 - 你可以吗？
- Yeah. - You can do that?
我不可以那样做
No. I cannot do that to her.
吉姆 不要做胆小鬼
Jim, get some fuckin' balls.
你连女孩裸照也不敢 怎跟她上床？
If you don't have the guts to photograph a naked chick, how you gonna sleep with one?
他虽然讨厌 但这次说得有道理
I don't like the kid, but he's got a point.
看 连回家拉屎的人也同意
See, even shit- brick knows you should do it.
你只需要搭条私人网线…
All you gotta do is set up some sort of private link or whatever on the 'Net…
把网址告诉我就行了
and tell me the address.
也顺便告诉我
You can send me the address too.
我留个座位给你
I'll save you a seat.
很好 唱得很好 但主音仍然弱点
Okay, that was good, but I want to thicken- up that solo.
星期六校际比赛 我想加强主音
Michigan State is this Saturday, and I want that part to smoke.
是 我知道 我承认水准欠佳
Yeah, I know, my timing's off.
不是欠佳而是需要男高音配合
No, it's not that. I think it'll work better as a duet with a tenor part.
我愿意唱男高音
I'll do it.
- 坏蛋 - 我愿意做
- Dick. - I'll do it.
好极 明天见
Great. See you tomorrow.
喂
Hmph.
- 你为什么这样做？- 因为我想唱
- Why are you doing this? - 'Cause I want to.
是吗？唱歌是不能弄虚作假
Yeah? Well, you can't fake this.
你最好用心练习
You better practice.
进来
Come in.
吉姆 嗯…有位小姐找你
Jim? There's a, uh… a young lady here to see you.
- 嘿 娜迪雅 - 嗨 吉姆 可以温习了吗？
- Hey, Nadia. - Hi, James. Ready to study?
哦 当然可以 他简直就是书虫
Oh, he's always ready to study. He's a real bookworm, this kid.
- 爸 - 但书虫并不等于书呆子
- Dad. - That means… He's not one of those nerdy guys but…
- 爸 - 不打扰你们温习了
- Dad! - Well, I'll… I'll let you two hit the books.
要啤酒吗？
You want a beer?
- 哦 开场了 - 走开啊
- Oh, there we go. - Come on, move!
哥哥 电脑是我的 我要用
Steve! It's my computer! And I wanna use it!
闭嘴
Shut up!
哦 你要换衣服 对不对？
Oh, you need to… You need to change, right?
- 嗯 介意吗？- 不不不 不介意
- Uhh, do you mind? - No. No, not at all.
嗯 请随便…开始更衣吧
Uh, please, you know. Just go ahead and get un… get changed.
我到楼下…嗯…先温习温习
I'll, uh… I'll go downstairs and start studying up.
- 好的 - 好
- Yeah. - Okay.
- 哦… - 办妥 开始了
- Oh… - All right, there he goes.
现在 我们开始了
Now, we're in business.
- 我一会就回来 - 吉姆 你到哪…
- Back in a sec. - Jimmy, honey, wh…
啊 她在那边
Ah, here she is.
- 我有没有错过什么 - 没有 你来得正是时候
- Did I miss anything? - No. You are just in time.
- 哦 哦 - 妙绝人寰
- Oh. Ohh! - This is incredible.
哦 天啊 太刺激了
Oh, my God! This is too much.
哦 脱一下少一件 脱一下少一件
Oh, did you see? Oh, there that goes. Oh, geez.
互联网 上帝保佑你
God bless the Internet.
- 啊 噫噫 - 开始脱吧
- Ai- yi- yi. - Do it. Take it off.
- 哦 天啊 - 噢…
- Oh, my God. - Ohhh!
哦 感谢主赐我们这样美妙的一天
Oh, thank you, God, for this wonderful, wonderful day.
她一定喝了很多木瓜汤
She takes her vitamins.
小心兴奋过头
Stop hyperventilating.
我从没见过这样精彩的镜头
This is, like, the coolest thing I've ever seen.
那还用说
I know.
史勒想出来的绝世妙计
Can you believe… This is definitely one of Stifler's best ideas ever.
她在…她在摸我的东西
What is she… She's touching my stuff.
- 她为什么在摸我的东西？- 由她摸
- Why is she touching my stuff? - Man, let her touch.
- 她在看我的东西 - 娜迪雅要摸就让她摸吧
- She's going through my stuff! - Nadia can touch anything she wants.
- 哦 - 哦不 哦不
- Oh. - Oh, no. Oh, no.
- 哦不 - 不错的藏书啊 吉姆
- No, no. - Oh, nice collection there, Jim.
她会走 她一定会走
She's gonna leave. She's definitely gonna…
她躺下来 她没走
She's getting comfortable. She's not gonna leave.
她正在看
She reads the articles.
是吗？
Is she?
她在自慰！
She's goin' downstairs.
- 噢 天哪 - 这次捡到宝了
- Oh, my God! - Jackpot, baby!
我有没有眼花？
Can you believe this?
我现在郑重宣布
I have an announcement that I would like to make.
有位美女…在我床上自慰
There is a gorgeous woman… masturbating on my bed!
- 谢谢你 娜迪雅 - 你想去吗 现在机不可失
- Thank you, Nadia! - If you ever had a chance with Nadia, this is it.
- 怎样去？凯文 - 勾引她
- What am I supposed to do, Kev? - Seduce her.
我…我该怎么说？
Wha… What the hell would I say?
回去问她要不要帮忙
Go over there and ask her if she needs an extra hand.
- 这样做好傻 我不能… - 傻？你错过才叫傻！
- That's stupid, Kev. I can't… - That's not stupid! You're stupid if you don't go!
去吧！有得吃就要吃！
Come on! Get over there!
- 快去 她准备好了 - 快走
- Get goin', man. She's prime. - Get out of here!
- 她等着你呢！- 好 我去
- She's waitin' for you. - Okay, all right. I'm goin'.
- 去 - 走啊 - 去！我走！
- Go! - Go! - I'm goin'!
- 走走走 - 哦 妈的
- Go! Go! Go! Go! - Oh, shit.
嘿 爸妈
Hey, Mom. Hey, Dad.
哦老天 哦上帝 哦糟糕 哦不
Oh, boy. Oh, God. Oh, crap. Oh, no.
你好？
Hello?
- 似乎吉姆写错了网址 - 什么？
- Looks like Jim addressed the e-mail wrong. - What?
现在全校都看到直播
It went out to every mailbox in the East High directory.
天啊 真幼稚
God, how juvenile.
嘿嘿嘿…各位
Hey, hey, hey, guys!
有东西看 哦 我的天啊 哇哦
Check this out! Oh, my God! Wow!
哦
Oh.
求求你 上帝 保佑我顺利求求你
Please, God, let this be it.
求求你了
Please?
有…有人进房间
S- Somebody's goin' in there.
对了 进去啦
Here you go. That's what you need to do.
- 这个小子和我是一班的 - 哦不
- That guy's in my trig class. - Oh, no.
- 你似乎要帮忙 - 吉姆！
- Looks like you could use an extra hand. - Jim!
- 呃…哦 天啊 - 下流
- Well… Oh, God. - Shame on you.
对 我下流 对不起 对不起
Yeah, shame on me. I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry.
- 我出去好了 - 好吧…
- Uh, you know, I'm just gonna go. - Well,
既然你看了我
you have seen me.
现在到我看你了
Now, it's my turn to see you.
脱
Strip!
- 脱？- 慢慢脱
- Strip? - Slowly.
嗯…你真的要我脱吗？
Uh, you mean, like, strip strip?
为我而脱
For me.
他们在说什么？
What is he talkin' to her about?
- 天知道 - 吉姆 加油 不要令观众失望
- Uh, no idea. - Come on, Jim. People are viewing. Get to business.
好极了
Perfect!
- 跳舞 吉姆 - 耶 好的 跳舞
- Move, James! Move! - Yeah, yeah. Move.
加油小子！今天是你的好日子
Go, trig boy! It's yer birthday!
- 不不不… - 求求你 上帝
- No! No. No. - Please, God.
什么事？
What's going on?
- 耶 - 还跳什么？还不冲过去
- Yes! - All right. Get in the mix!
- 看那里 - 哦 好的
- See there. - Oh, okay.
- 真呕心！- 搞什么鬼？
- This is disgusting. - What the fuck is this?
不要跳了
Cut it out, man!
耶
Yeah.
神经病
Freak.
连椅子都用了
Did not just take out that chair.
- 什么都用了 - 再脱 再脱 你真坏
- Yup, he took out the chair. - More, more, you bad boy!
哦对 我好坏 我好坏 嘿呀
Oh, yeah, I'm naughty. I'm naughty, baby. Hyah!
噢 天啊
Ohh, God!
现在…
Now,
来我这里
come to me.
哦 好
Oh, yeah.
- 要开始了 - 这才对嘛
- Here we go. - He's in, man.
好戏要上演了
This just got a hell of a lot better.
- 温柔点 - 好
- Be gentle. - Okay.
嗯…
Uh…
哦
Oh.
吉姆？
Jim?
- 哦…不 - 哦 不
- Oh! Oh, no. - Oh, no.
- 哦 喔 - 升空中止
- Oh. Ohh! - Liftoff aborted.
- 休斯敦 我们遇到问题了 - 哦 嗯…
- Houston, we have a problem. - Oh… Uhh…
什么事？他怎样了？
What happened? What did he do
枪走火了
He blew it.
我想我还是走了
I guess I'll be going now.
不不不…不要走 我还没完 我还有储备
No, no, no, I'm… I'm not done, Nadia. I've, uh… I've got reserves.
娜迪雅 不要 求求你
Nadia, please, please. I'm begging you.
我倒喜欢你的黄色书刊
Well, I do like your dirty magazines.
你喜欢？有没有看过这本？
You do? Okay. Well. Um. Did- Did… Did you see this one?
这本更色情露骨
This here is your… is your more, uh, exotic, risque magazine.
- 出动到黄色书刊 - 狗急跳墙
- He's pullin' out the porn. - He's desperate.
吉姆 她走后你可以看个够
Jim, just wait till she leaves.
里面的女人好性感
Very arousing women. They arouse me…
我看见就兴奋
They arouse me very, very much.
但…都不如你 我看见你更兴奋
But, uh… But not as arousing as you.
- 噢 吉姆 - 哦 天哪！
- Oh, Jim! - Oh, God!
耶
Yes!
再次交锋 喔
He's ruining daisy! Whoo!
是不是叫剃毛头？
So, uh, "shaved" is the expression?
厉害
Holy shit.
- 厉害 - 厉害
- Holy shit! - Holy shit!
- 厉…害 - 抚摸我 吉姆
- H- H- Holy shit! - Touch me, Jim.
这里
Here.
哦 喔
Oh. Oh.
- 又来了？- 糟糕 又来了
- Again? - Not again.
- 又来了 - 可能吗？
- Not again, man! - Is that possible?
真没用
What a loser.
嘿
Hey!
- 嘿 牛奶男孩 - 闭嘴
- Hey, minute man! - Shut up.
你应该鼓励我才对
You know… You know you're supposed to be supportive.
你还有机会再追娜迪雅吗？
Hey, you think you still got a chance with Nadia?
没戏了 她的监护人在网上看到
No. Her sponsors here saw the thing on the 'Net.
我想大概不高兴了
I- I really don't think they liked it.
你怎么知道？
How do you know that?
她正在坐飞机回捷克
She's already on a plane back home.
噢
Yeah.
也许…或者我不适合交女朋友
You know, guys? Maybe I'm just not good with girls, period.
不不…真的…就像是先天性性缺陷
No- no- no, really- really. Like… Like I was born without that part of the brain.
我是说 不能跟女孩聊天
I mean, I can't talk to girls.
跟女孩交谈 我一开口会说错话
And when I do talk to them, I screw it up.
毕业舞会快到 找借口于事无补
Yeah, well, come prom those excuses aren't going to do you any good.
有一次的音乐营
And one time at band camp,
我们玩猫捉老鼠
we weren't supposed to have pillow fights,
但我们不得不打一个枕头 真好玩
but we had a pillow fight, and it was so much fun.
而那次 我们遗失了乐谱 却又记不起乐章
A- And this one time, we all lost our music and we were supposed to play this song,
于是乱奏一通 不断的奏
but we didn't know it, so we just made it up and we kept playing and playing,
指挥莫名其妙 真好玩
and the conductor didn't know what we were doing, and it was so funny.
你在生气吗？
So, you're pissed about somethin', huh.
我一生气就用横笛吹巴赫
You know what I do when I'm angry?
吹几下就心平气和
I just play some Bach on my flute. It's so relaxing.
- 就是在那次音乐营时候学的 - 等一等 嗯…
- I learned to do that at band camp. - Hold on, uh…
你不知道我在生什么气
You have no idea why I'm angry?
因为明天测验？有时候我也会…
Is it because we have a test tomorrow? Sometimes I get cranky…
我每逢测试都心情恶劣
when I know I have a big test to study for.
- 对了 肯定是测验的缘故 - 我也认为
- Yeah. Yeah, that's pretty much it. - I thought so…
- 那次在音乐营… - 你叫什么？
- because this one time at band camp… - What's your name?
- 蜜雪儿 - 好的
- Michelle. - Okay.
蜜雪儿 嗯…
Michelle, um…
你肯做我的舞伴吗？
Do you want to be my date for the prom?
做你舞件？你真的邀请我？
Really? You seriously want to go with me?
真的邀请你
Yes. Seriously.
舞会后去史勒的派对 好吗？那一定更酷
Are we going to Steve Stifler's party afterwards? Because that would be so cool.
- 好 只要你喜欢 - 好呀 我们会好开心
- Sure, whatever you want. - Cool! We're gonna have such a good time.
就像有一次音乐营的野火会…
It'll be like this one time at band camp when we all had a campfire…
嗨
Hi.
- 你怎知道我在这里？- 史勒告诉我
- How'd you know I was here? - Stifler told me.
- 你问史勒？- 我想找你
- Talked to Stifler? - Well, I needed to find you.
我们要练歌
We're gonna have to work on that song.
好的 很高兴你来
Okay. I'm glad you came by.
你开夜班？
So you work nights?
- 我爸爸是这里的经理 - 真的？
- My dad's the manager. - Really?
太好了 他的三文治真好吃
Cool. Tell him the subs are great.
- 你明年上密西根大学？- 是的
- So you're going to Michigan next year? - Yeah.
爸妈希望我能够上西北大学
My parents want me to go to Northwestern, but…
西北要我作一篇文章
I don't wanna write all those extra essays they make you do.
我懒得去作 题目叫「感情最珍贵的一刻」
I mean, how am I supposed to know what my "most emotionally significant moment" was?
所以密大一答应收我 我就选密大
So when my "U" of "M" acceptance came in December, I just said the hell with it.
- 洋葱 - 什么？
- Onions? - What?
要洋葱吗？
You, uh, want onions?
不要 谢谢
Oh, no, thank you.
你打算主修哪科？
So what are you gonna major in?
州立大学的商科 我会加入大学的球队
State's got a good business school, and I could probably walk- on to the lacrosse team.
你什么都安排好了 对吧？
Well, you've probably got it pretty figured out, then, huh?
读商科 打球 我都有兴趣
I mean, business is okay, and lacrosse is awesome, but…
至于会不会做职业球员
what am I gonna be, a professional lacrosse player?
我也拿不定主意
I really have no idea.
我还以为只有自己才没主意
Thank God. I thought I was the only one.
不只你一个
Well, you're not.
那么 明年我们会很接近
So we're gonna be close next year.
你指我们的两间大学很接近？
You mean East Lansing and Ann Arbor?
是的
Yeah.
你觉得怎么样？
What are you talkin' about?
我不能做你舞会的舞伴 我要等另一个人邀请
I can't go to the prom with you. I'm holding out for someone else.
你在开玩笑吧
You gotta be fuckin' kidding me.
我希望芬奇肯邀请我
I know it's a long shot, but I figure Paul Finch might ask me.
芬奇 回家拉屎的人
Finch. Shit- brick.
哦 我一时忘记说了
Oh, gosh. I- I forgot.
你复原得很好
You look okay.
我是说 脸上没有留下疤痕
I- I mean, the scars healed really well.
- 嘿 史勒 - 去死！
- Hey, Stifler. - Eat shit.
什么回事？
What was that all about?
- 他被芬奇打过 觉得很没面子 - 谁告诉你的？
- He's still embarrassed because Finch kicked his ass. - Who told you that?
什么意思？「无可奉告」？
What do you mean, "no comment"?
- 你和芬奇有一腿吗？- 开什么玩笑 当然没有
- Did you two hook up or something? - What, are you kidding? No.
为什么说芬奇那样威猛？
Then how did all this get started?
好吧 现在说穿了也无所谓
Well, I guess it's all right for me to tell you now.
反正他已经威尽了…帮我拿点奶酪
That reputation of his isn't going anywhere. Cheese, please.
芬奇找到我说
Finch comes up to me and says, "Jessica,
需要我的帮助 一大堆废话
I need your help with this, blah, blah, etcetera."
我就说：「可以 给我200块
So I said, "All right. Pay me 200 bucks,
我向女生说你床上功夫一级棒「
and I'll tell a couple of girls that you're dynamite in bed."
他给钱 我说好话
So he did, and I did.
- 有效果吗？- 当然有效
- That actually works? - Well, duh! Of course.
实际上 我添油加醋
Naturally, I embellished a little bit.
你听说芬奇和成熟的女人搞上了吗？
Did you hear that Finch had an affair with an older woman?
不 这我倒没听过
No, I didn't hear that one.
那是我得意之作
That one was my favorite.
上过啦啦队队长
Do that cheerleader.
她想要我 她打电话给我…
She wants me. She calls me up…
哦 天啊 原来你是同性恋
Oh, my God, you're gay!
一起唱嘛 你知道歌词
Sing it with me. You know the words.
你想得倒美 你日唱夜唱 唱足一星期
No, thanks, man. You've been singin' that shit all week.
星期六出赛 不准你再唱
If you try that at M.S.U. This Saturday, I'll kick your ass.
星期六最后一场球赛
Our last game is this Saturday.
当然 哦 糟糕
Yeah, well, shit.
我有场重要球赛 最后一场
I've got this lacrosse game. It's really important. It's our last game.
上次中区打赢 今次我要还击
Central almost beat us last time, so this time I really wanna kick their ass.
赛事在州立大学举行
But it's gonna be cool, because the game's at State,
赛后我可以去听你们演唱
which means afterwards I'll be able to stop by.
那么 你不能参加演唱了
So you can't sing at the competition.
对不起 我今趟无法参加
Heather, I'm sorry. I totally blew it.
不要紧 你应该选择你的兴趣
It's okay. You should… do what makes you happy.
好的 谢谢你能谅解
All right. Listen, thanks for understanding.
好
Yeah.
那么 再见了
So, uh, I guess I'll see you later?
嗯
Mm- hmm.
嘿 凯文
Hey, Kevin.
- 有没有见过回家拉屎的人吗？- 怎么了？他得罪了你？
- You seen shit-brick lately? - Why? What did you do to him?
得罪我？怎会得罪我？
Me? Nothing.
他打我打到我怕嘛
See, I'm the one whose ass he kicked.
不过我可以告诉你一件事
But, uh, I'll tell you one thing, though.
从此他要在校厕拉屎了
I don't think he's gonna have a problem shitting in school anymore.
我在他的朱古力奶下了泻药
Slipped a little something into his mochaccino.
哦天
Oh, God!
哦 哦
Oh! Oh!
天啊
Jesus.
这边请 先生
Right this way, sir.
哦天
Oh, God!
哦 不
Oh, no.
毕业舞会肯定会很好玩
It's gonna be fun.
好玩？乐队差劲 布置九流
You know it's just gonna be some crappy band and stupid decorations.
你没有舞伴才这样说
You're just saying that because prom's a week away and you don't have a date.
不不…我不用舞伴
No, no, no. I don't want a date.
芬奇单身去参加 我也是
Finch is goin' stag and… so am I.
芬奇真潇洒啊
God, he's like so… refined.
他真的搭上年长女人？
You think that older woman thing is true?
真的 对方是史勒的妈妈
Yeah, it's true. It was Stifler's mom.
钟妮 你制造的噪音？
Joanie, was that you?
- 哦 - 忍无可忍
- Oh! - Can't hold it.
哦
Oh!
呃
Eww!
耶
Yeah!
凯文 今学期我们的感情
Kev? I think we've come…
- 深厚了不少 - 是啊 确实
- a really long way since homecoming. - Yeah, we have.
也行是时候…
Maybe it's time…
我们也许应该用新方法去表达
we start to express ourselves in new ways.
- 是 - 你愿意吗？
- Yeah. - You wanna do it?
- 愿意 - 我爱你
- Yeah. - I love you.
到你说了
It's your turn.
我想不到你指这方面
That's not what I was thinking.
你只想到性 满脑子都是
Sex. It's always about sex.
不是满脑子都是
It's not always about sex.
我只是会错意
I just thought it was about sex this time.
维琪 人人都随便说 我爱你 我爱你
Look, Vicky, love is a term that gets thrown around,
但毫无诚意
and- and people don't mean it.
当我说的时候 我不想这样
When I say it, I want it to be more than words.
- 你知道吗？- 我要等… - 完美的时刻
- You know? - I want it to be… - Perfect.
对极了
Exactly.
- 好 准备好了吗？- 准备好了
- Okay, Albert. You ready? - No problemo.
来 海瑟 合作一点好吗？
Come on, Heather. Work with me here.
入球 8号欧兹
Goal, Ostreicher!
- 好极了 欧兹 - 做得好 欧兹
- All right, Oz! - Atta boy, Ozzie!
喔 耶 大家上
Whoo! Yeah, baby!
- 打败他们 - 来吧 伙计们
- We're crushing you losers! - Let's go, fellas!
来吧 哇哦
Come on! Whoo- hoo!
集中精神 培养乐感
Focus on the music. Think melody.
- 让音乐成为我的指导 - 这将是一个开始
- Let the music be my guide. - That would be a start.
那是谁？史勒
Who's the man? Stifler!
大家围过来 大家围过来
Huddle up, guys! Huddle up!
大家围过来 来
Huddle up! Come on! Okay.
好了 好了
All right, all right!
- 很好的冲撞 各位 - 很好的冲撞
- Good hustle, guys. - Good hustle.
你们有拼搏精神 但你们依然可能输
But you can still lose. You all saw what happened to Oz out there.
你们都看见欧兹的情形 你们不要以为奉旨入球
I don't want to ever see any of you thinking you're gonna score.
等真正进了球
You don't score until you score.
- 才算进球 - 对了 说得对
- Until you score. - That's right, baby!
今天是最后关头
It all boils down to today.
你们这班毕业生苦练四年
For you seniors, this marks the culmination…
- 就是为了今天 - 高潮日
- of the past four years. - Culmination.
今天的球赛对你们意义重大
I want you to think about what this means to you.
打赢了 会给你们留下美好回忆
Do you guys wanna look back on your days at East…
你们要不要美好回忆？
and know that you used the time you had?
- 我们要 - 这就对了
- Hell, yeah! - You do!
- 好态度 欧兹 - 祝大家好运
- Ah! Good attitude, Ostreicher. - Good luck, fellas.
我没有叫你走
Christ, I didn't tell ya to leave the game.
对不起 教练
I'm sorry, Coach.
你有更重要的地方要去？
You got someplace more important to be, Ostreicher?
是的
Yeah.
欧兹
Ostreicher!
欧兹 混蛋
Oz? Fuckface?
欧兹
Ostreicher!
- 嘿 欧兹！- 欧兹
- Hey, Oz! - Ozmeister!
- 哦 太好了 - 那球赛呢？
- Oh, great. - What about the game?
- 我不出赛了 - 为我们而放弃球赛？
- I'm not playing. - You're missing the game for us?
不 为你而放弃球赛
No, I'm missing the game for you.
- 意思是我不能唱主音？- 阿拨 你唱得好难听
- Does this mean I'm not gonna get to do the duet? - Albert, you suck.
他不会回来
I don't think he's comin' back.
耶 欧兹 好棒啊！
Yeah, Oz! You fuckin' rule!
- 太棒了！- 耶
- Fuckin' rule! - Yeah!
说与不说并不重要
Maybe the words aren't that important.
我知道他是真的关心我 知道吗？
It's like, I know he really cares about me, you know?
他即使不说出口 其实是爱我的
Even if he can't say it, he does.
虽然总想上床 但他是男孩嘛 对吧？
And yeah, he always talks about sex, but that's okay, 'cause he's a guy, right?
- 他如果是男孩就该有那种冲动 - 没错
- He's got a dick. He's a guy. - Right.
功课这样做 你认为妥当吗？
Wait. Is this translation right?
回家吧 我受够了
"Go home, bird teacher. I've had enough."
不知道 我是抄凯文的
I don't know. I got it from Kevin.
- 那么 痛不痛？- 什么？
- So, does it hurt? - What?
那回事 痛不痛？
You know… sex. Does it hurt?
痛 初次会痛 你知道的
Yeah. I mean, the first time you do it, you know, it hurts.
但做完再做 再做 再再做…
But then you, you do it again and again and again…
越做越舒服 舒服到不得了
It just starts to feel good. Really good.
来个假设 假设我不做
Okay, so say I don't do it.
然后上大学 可能看走眼了
And then I go off to college. I might end up doing it with some random guy…
- 失身给个坏蛋 - 有道理
- who totally turns out to be a jerk. - This is true.
到时我会后悔没有跟凯文做
And I'll wish I would've done it with Kevin.
那就跟凯文做吧
So go do it with Kevin.
- 你赞成？- 你已经有准备了
- You think? - Yeah. You're… You're ready.
- 有性行为好正常 你已经准备好了 - 你说得对
- You're woman. Look at you. You're ready for sex. - You're right.
- 好吧 - 会有一个完美的性行为
- Now. - And it's gonna be right, and it's gonna be just perfect.
- 完美的性 - 谢谢你 杰西卡
- Perfect sex. - Thanks, Jessica.
不要客气
Please.
凯文
Kevin.
- 我想做爱 - 现在？
- I wanna have sex. - Now?
毕业晚会
Prom.
今晚是大日子 你一定很欢喜
You must be excited about the big night tonight.
简直狂喜
Thrilled.
幸运女朗叫什么？
Who's the lucky girl?
蜜雪儿
Michelle.
- 蜜雪儿 - 是的
- Michelle. - Yeah.
- 她一定很特别 - 的确特别
- She must be very special. - Oh, she's special, all right.
否则也不会被你看中
I'm sure she is special if you picked her out of the whole bunch.
吉姆 你出发前…
Jim, I'm just gonna say one thing…
我想说句话
before you leave tonight.
你要万分 万分小心
I want you to be very, very careful…
当你戴上
when you're putting on…
安全套的时候
the corsage.
好的 爸爸
Okay, Dad.
- 答应我 - 我答应你
- Promise me. - I promise.
音乐营我们也有舞跳
You know, at band camp we have dances like this,
但跳得更好玩
only they're way funner.
进展报告 大家的成绩如何？
All right, status check. Where do you guys stand?
芬奇 喝酒逃避不是办法
Finch, we know where you are, but can't really use that as an excuse.
吉姆？
Jim?
我的女伴是个音乐怪胎 不用再说下去了吧？
Uh, my date's a flute- toting band dork. Does that answer your question?
欧兹 唱歌追得到妞吗？
Oz, is this vocal- jazz shit gonna pay off or what?
凯文 你算什么态度？
Kevin, what's with the attitude?
态度？我的态度？
Attitude? Me?
你们的态度才有问题
I think you guys should be a little more enthusiastic.
好不容易等到今晚
This is the night we've been waiting for.
怎可以退缩？
We're in this together. You guys can't back out.
凯文 你要我们陪才敢做 你害怕了？
Kev, you don't need us to get laid. Are you afraid or something?
不 我们说过共同进退嘛
No. Come on. We made a pact.
你们不可以违约 这是必须的
You can't break that. You guys are gonna have to…
必须什么？什么也没需要！
Have to what, Kev, huh? I don't have to do shit.
这样的压力既讨厌又无聊
Forget it already. I am so sick and tired of all this bullshit pressure.
我虽然没有性经验 我已经无法忍受 我讨厌性
I've never even had sex, and already, I can't stand it. I hate sex!
我不会傻呼呼的站在这里
And I'm not gonna stand around here busting my balls over something that,
坦白地说 那些不重要
quite frankly, isn't that damn important.
我要回去找那怪女孩
I'm gonna go hang out with that geek over there…
起码她不会开口闭口都是性
'cause at least she has something else to talk about besides sex.
太过份了
Goddamn.
是
Yeah.
起码我习惯了在校厕扎马
You know, at least I learned how to shit in school, buddy.
嘿 芬奇
Hey, Finch.
- 想跳舞吗？- 好
- Wanna dance? - Yeah.
- 你没有舞伴吗？- 我喜欢追男孩
- How come you have no date? - I like to keep my options open.
我有份礼物给你
I got something for you.
是个安慰奖
Consider it a consolation prize.
谢谢你 杰西卡
Jessica, this is great! Wow!
- 我收了你的钱 问心有愧 - 200块全花在酒瓶上？
- Felt sorta guilty about taking your money. - You spent $200 on this?
不 50块买酒瓶 150块买耳环
No, I spent 50 on the flask, 150 on the earrings.
- 那么…嗯… - 事先声明
- These are, uh… - Let me just clarify…
- 不要打我主意 芬奇 - 当然不会
- that you have no chance of scoring with me, Finch. - Of course not!
你和雪门很熟吗 嗯？
So I take it you and Sherman are pretty close, huh?
在派对认识 对吧？
You met at that party a while back, right?
是的 那晚我们谈心
Yeah, we were up all night together.
谈个一个通宵
We had one of those amazingly deep conversations…
互相了解了不少
where you feel like you really get to know someone.
谈心？
Deep conversation, huh?
你把那回事叫做谈心？
Is that what you call it?
还可以叫什么？
What else would I call it?
谢谢 各位同学
Thank you, Great Falls.
我们现在休息一会儿
We're gonna take a little break. You are beautiful.
你真恶心
You suck!
各位 打扰一下
Excuse me, everyone.
很抱歉
Sorry to interrupt.
我认为有件事你们应该知道
I just thought you all should know this.
雪门是个大话精
Chuck Sherman is a liar.
我从没跟他发生过关系
I never had sex with him.
他也从没跟任何人发生过关系 我知道 因为他亲口对我说过
He's never had sex with anyone. I know this because he told me.
他说 最多是使用西柚弄一弄
Once he tried to screw a grapefruit, but that's all.
哦 他也说 他一急就会屎裤子
Oh. He also told me that when he gets nervous, he sometimes wets his pants.
打扰你们了 对不起
Thank you for your time.
- 怎么一个人在这里？- 我觉得没意思
- Guess what? - Not interested.
算了 准备去史勒别墅吧
Kevin. Come on, man. The bus to Stifler's is gonna be here soon.
- 我不去 - 什么？
- I'm not going. - What?
为什么？
Why not?
想不到出现这种情形
Look, things didn't really turn out how I wanted them to.
我连自己在做什么都不知道
I mean, I don't even know what I'm doin'.
我本来满有把握
I- I'm acting like I've got everything together tonight.
但维琪会问我爱不爱她
I know that Vicky's gonna ask me if I love her, and…
我不知道怎样回答
I don't know what I'm gonna say.
我就快如愿以偿
I mean, I'm on the brink.
就快可以做了 本应欢欢天喜地
I'm just about to do it. I should be psyched.
或者你说得对 我害怕
I don't know. Maybe you're right. Maybe I am just scared.
不要消极了 今晚是大日子
Come on, Kev. Tonight is the night.
我们等足四年 终于开完舞会
We- We are finally going to a post- prom party on the lake.
到史勒的别墅去
We have been waiting for this for four years.
否则何必交史勒那种朋友？
Why else have we been friends with Stifler all this time, right?
史勒是我们的朋友？
We were friends with Stifler?
嘿 听着
Hey, look.
原来雪门还是处男
Sherman didn't even get laid.
- 他没有做过？- 而且当众屎湿裤子
- He didn't? - No, he pissed himself.
什么？
What?
上车才告诉你
We'll tell you on the bus.
我回去拿睡袋
I'm gonna go inside and grab my bag.
或者该带那怪妞出来
My date too, perhaps?
史勒的妈妈离了婚 分得这别墅
Stifler's mom got it in the divorce.
有次音乐营…
That reminds me of this one time…
可以问你一句话吗？
Hey, can I ask you a question?
为什么只有我说故事？
How come you don't have any stories? I've got lots of them,
你很少出声
and you don't have any.
哦 我也有很多故事 相信我…
Oh, I've got stories. Believe me. They're just, uh…
但没有音乐营那样纯情
They're just a little more risque than tales of band camp.
男孩之间的黄色故事？说来听斩
Are they gross or something? Like guy stuff? Tell me!
你既然要听 我说好了
Okay. You want a story?
史勒喝过一杯加「料」的啤酒
Here's a story. Stifler finds this beer…
- 全屋最好的房间 - 凯文 这很完美
- This is the nicest room in the house. - Kev, it's perfect.
你们打算做爱
You guys are gonna fuck, aren't ya?
下流仔 下流女
Fuckers! Fuckers, fuckers!
Fuckers, fuckers, fuckers!
- 出去 - 我想看
- Out. - Aw, come on!
我有句话要说 海瑟
There's something I've been meaning to tell you, Heather.
什么？
What's that?
我不轻易说出口 但…
It's gonna sound really bad, but, uh,
我想你知道
I want you to know.
知道吗
You see, uh,
我是处男
I'm a virgin, and, uh…
我 凯文 吉姆 芬奇
Well, me, Kevin, Jim and Finch were…
大家约定
We all made this pact…
我们争取在中学毕业前
that we would lose our virginity…
争取性经验
before high school was over,
我们打算今晚做
and tonight is supposed to be the night that we all do it.
这样的暗示方法不算最好吧？
This isn't the best way to proposition me.
不是 我的意思是
No, that's… That's not what I mean.
我是说…
W- What I mean is, uh…
听着 你知道我为什么退出球赛吗？
Look, do you know what made me leave that game?
听到教练对我们说
See, Coach, he was givin' us this speech about…
有机会入球 就要乘胜追击
not slacking off when you see the opportunity to score…
你这样说不见得会好些
This isn't any better, Chris.
不是 我的意思是
No, you see… You see, Heather,
我觉得跟你一起
what I realized is that…
我不是在进攻龙门
with you, it's… not like I'm running towards a goal…
不是在设法入球
looking for the best way to score.
说出来老土 但是…
This may sound a little corny, but…
我觉得自己已经胜出
I feel like I've already won.
对我来说 你很重要
And, uh, I care about you a lot.
欧兹 我知道
Oz, I know.
- 你叫我欧兹？- 是的
- You called me Oz. - Well, yeah.
你的朋友个个都叫你欧兹
It's what your friends call you.
我觉得自己是你的朋友
I mean, I feel like I'm one of your friends now.
你的女朋友
And… your girlfriend?
（非请勿进）
走失了？
Are ya lost?
你是史勒的妈妈…？
You're Stifler's mom. Uh…
不是走失了 只是…
No, no, not lost. Just, um,
到处逛逛
you know, taking the tour.
谢谢你容许我们来开派对
Hey, uh, thank you for letting us have this wonderful party.
我的儿子不准我反对
As if there was an alternative in the matter.
玩得开心吗？
So, you enjoying yourself?
伯母 我喝得有点飘飘然
I'm… three sheets to the wind, ma'am.
那就好
I'm so happy for you.
酒可以松弛神经
But it takes the edge off, doesn't it?
- 你的小女伴呢？- 我约不到女伴
- Where's your little date tonight? - No date. It was…
因为一宗厕所事件
It was a bathroom incident.
- 什么？- 算了
- Pardon me? - Never mind.
有没有东西喝？
You have anything to drink?
啤酒在楼上
I believe the kegs are upstairs.
啤酒是小儿科 我要正货
That is what the cretins drink.
要够劲的那种
I'm talking about alcohol, liquor.
- 很好 - 可以
- The good stuff. - All right.
我有些威士忌
I got some scotch.
- 丹麦酿制？- 18年
- Single malt? - Aged 18 years.
我喜欢的年龄
The way I like it.
到酒橱去拿杯吧
Why don't you go grab a glass from the bar?
我想我会的
I think I should.
我帮你斟
Allow me.
开一个派对
You know it's a bitchin' party.
是我史勒的拿手好戏
The Stif- man always comes through in the clutch.
后来他连黄胆水也呕出来
And then he just puked his brains out.
- 真难看 - 早就警告过你
- That is a nasty story. - Yep, I told you.
我也有黄色故事 ？
Do you want to hear a nasty story of mine?
有兴趣听吗
It's sort of sexual.
好啊 说来听听
Yeah! Yeah, let's hear it.
有一次音乐营…我们玩转杯游戏
Okay, well, this one time at band camp, we were playing this game.
杯口指中谁就要吻谁
I don't know if you know it, but it's called "Spin the Bottle."
结果我要吻一个叫温特的人
And I had to kiss this guy named Mark Wander on the lips.
温特是个喇叭手
And- And he plays trombone…
你想怎样做？
So how do you want to be?
什么姿势？
Like… how do you want to do it?
不知道 你呢？
I don't know. How do you?
一般…正常的姿势 男上女下
Like… normal style. The missionary position.
好的
Okay.
凯文
Kev?
- 什么？- 我想听你说
- Yeah? - I wanna hear you say it.
好的
Okay.
维琪
Victoria,
我爱你
I love you.
我的头发
Oh. My hair.
痛不痛？
You okay?
放慢点
Yeah. Go slow.
结果就是 你要吻他20秒
So the end of the story is you…
是啊 而他呆头呆脑
had to kiss the guy for 20 seconds.
人人都玩起来
Yes! And he was such a dork. Everyone laughed at me…
- 情形也的确滑稽 - 明白了
- but I didn't care because it was so funny. - I get it.
有次音乐会 我用横笛来解决
And this one time at band camp, I stuck a flute in my pussy.
嗯
Hmm.
什么？
Excuse me?
你以为我不懂发泄吗？
What? You don't think I know how to get myself off?
音乐营内也有性教育
Hell, that's what half of band camp is… Sex Ed.
可以开始吗？等得我不耐烦了
So are we gonna screw soon, 'cause I'm gettin' kinda antsy.
用这间房吧
This'll do. Whoo- hoo!
噢
Ow!
戴两个上去 不会那么敏感
Now, I have two rubbers. Wear them both. It'll desensitize you.
我不要你早泄
I don't want you coming so damn early this time.
为什么以为我会早泄？
What makes you think that I would come early?
我在互联网看过你
Come on. I saw you on the 'Net. Why do you think I accepted this date?
我知道十拿九稳才跟你来
You're a sure thing.
说得对
Yes, I am.
于是我说：这分明是…「文艺复兴时代的作品」
So I said, "This is very obviously a Piero della Francesca."
嗯
Hmm.
我恭维你风情万种 你介意吗？
So, uh, would you object if I said that you were quite striking?
芬奇先生 你想勾引我？
Mr. Finch, are you trying to seduce me?
正是 伯母
Yes, ma'am, I am.
嗯…你死定了
Mmm, you're dead.
- 想不到你这样行 - 我也是
- I had no idea you'd be this good. - Neither did I.
哦 芬奇 芬奇
Oh, Finchy. Finch.
- 哦 史勒妈妈 - 芬奇
- Oh, Stifler's mom, whoa! - Finchy!
开始了
Okay, let's go.
我叫什么？我要你叫我一声！
What's my name? Say my name, bitch!
蜜雪儿 蜜雪儿
Michelle, Michelle.
天哪
Oh, God.
昨晚是难忘的一夜
That was a great night, huh?
是的
Yeah.
转眼就举行毕业舞会
I mean, I just can't believe we had our senior prom.
对 时间过得真快
I know. It went by so fast.
对
Yeah, it did.
凯文
Kevin?
明年你去密西根升学
Next year with you going to Ann Arbor…
我去纽约
and me going to Ithaca,
我们不得不分手了
it's not gonna work, is it?
不要那样说
No. Don't say that.
我们可以见面
I mean, we could make it work.
- 会行得通的 - 不会 凯文
- It'll be perfect. - No, Kevin.
- 但是… - 我刚明白到
- But… - See, that's what I've been realizing…
世事没有完美
is that… nothing's perfect.
将来的事谁也难预料
And you can't plan everything.
你我会天南地北
Well, I guess… you will be pretty far away.
各自交新朋友
And we'll be on our own, meeting new people.
可是 昨晚
Last night, though.
我没骗你
I wasn't lying.
我知道
I know.
她走掉了
She's gone. Wha…
哦 惨了 我被利用了
Oh, my God. She used me.
我被利用了
I was used.
我被利用了厉害
I was used. Cool!
为什么锁着门？
What's this door locked…
妈 你在哪…
Mom, where's…
- 妈？回家拉屎的人？- 嘿 史勒
- Mom? Shit-brick? - Hey, Stifler.
不得不承认 女人
I just gotta say that women,
像美酒 愈老愈醇
like a fine wine, only get better with age.
当然 我无从比较 不过 嗯…
Of course, I have no basis for comparison, but, uh,
实在不俗
it was good.
你还是处男 欧兹？
So you almost made it, huh, Oz?
- 我们渡过温馨的一晚 - 再接再励
- I'll just say that we had a great night together. - Hang in there, buddy.
- 你迟早会得偿所愿 - 我相信我们已经堕入爱河
- You'll get there. - You know, guys, I think we're falling in love.
哇…哦…
Wha… Wow.
太好了 值得高兴
That's great, man. That's awesome.
最美好的时光是何时？
Y- You know what the coolest thing is, guys?
就是此时此刻
This. You know, right now.
对 从今以后一切都不同
It's true. I mean, after this, everything's gonna be different.
因为开了斋？
After… getting laid?
- 因为中学毕了业 - 往前迈进
- After high school. - Here's to the next step.
- 往前迈进 向前迈进 - 向前迈进 - 向前迈进
- To the next step. - To the next step. - To the next step.
甜心？
Sweetheart?